# kamal pandey

Senior Software Engineer

9892350221, 8421033975



Ambernath Pale Gaon, Ambernath(E), Thane, India

6.5+ years of experience working in a corporate environment as a front-end UI/Web developer. Experience in system analysis, design, workflow architecture, development, testing and maintenance of web based applications. Experience in developing interactive web applications utilizing Angular 2+ and above ,React. JS HTML5, CSS,RXJS, JSON, and integrating Restful API's Or GraphQl. Having a knowledge of developing end to end application with front end and backend using Node. Js Express and mongoDb with deployment In depth knowledge of web technologies and standards to deliver the best experiences across web and mobile devices including responsive Web UI.

### WORK EXPERIENCE

# Senior Software Engineer

LTI - Larsen & Toubro Infotech · Full-time

10/2021 - Present

Mumbai, INDIA

IT Services and IT Consulting

Tasks

- Working as a Fronted developer, creating angular projects as per client's requirements using Angular12, JSON, HTML5, and SCSS. Responsible for creating efficient design and developing User Interaction screens using Angular or ReactJs, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JSON, RXJS, NGRX

Contact: Vijay Bodake - 8626062174

## Associate Consultant

Capgemini Information Technologies Pvt. Ltd. Airoli

07/2019 - 10/2021

Mumbai, INDIA

Tasks

- Working as a Frontend developer, creating angular projects as per client's requirements using Angular7,, JSON, HTML, CSS. Responsible for creating efficient design and developing User Interaction screens using Angular, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JSON

Contact: Raghvendra Nayak - 9930544508

# Jr. Programmer

Proteus Technologies Pvt. Ltd.

03/2017 - 07/2019

Mumbai, INDIA

Product based company

Achievements/Tasks

Working as a full stack developer, creating angular projects as per client's requirements using Angular4, Java, Restful web services, Hibernate, JSON, HTML, and CSS. Responsible for creating efficient design and developing User Interaction screens using Angular, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and JSON

# **EDUCATION**

# Bachelor Of Engineer in Electronics and **Telecommunication**

Mumbai University

06/2012 - 05/2016

Mumbai

## **SKILLS**



# INDUSTRIAL PROJECTS

Paramount (08/2022 - Present)

- Technologies: Angular 12+, HTML5, SCSS, GraphQL, NGRX, RXJS, NodeJS, GIT,
- **Responsibilities**: Application Development, Code Testing.
- **Description**: Worked as contractor basis to develop the application which track all the tv shows movies with details

Viacom CBS (11/2021 - 08/2022)

- Technologies: React JS, HTML5, SCSS, RestService, NodeJS.
- Responsibilities: Application Development, Code Testing.
- **Description**: Worked as contractor basis to develop the application which track all the tv shows movies with details

#### German Public Sector (07/2019 - 09/2021)

- Technologies: Angular7+, JavaScript, HTML5, SCSS, JASMINE, KARMA, GIT, JIRA, JAVA
- Responsibilities: Application Development, Code testing (Unit, Automation)
- **Description**: German federal chamber of civil law notaries, aims to go fully digital by 2022. Our aim was to create a multi-module application to achieve that purpose. We also wrote a spectrum of test to provide a complete quality application.

#### Content Library Dashboard (06/2018 - 06/2019)

- Technologies: Angular2+, JavaScript, HTML5, SCSS, JAVA
- Responsibilities: Developing Module and unit testing. Designing of Application using Angular 6 to design the process and core java to handle the process requests.
- **Description**: Dashboard which shows user's attached contents where user can add, disable and view contents. A content can be any file (image, video, pdf, zip etc).

#### Ecommerce Project. (04/2017 - 06/2018)

- Technologies: Angular2+, JavaScript, HTML5, SCSS, JAVA
- **Responsibilities**: Developing Module and unit testing. Designing of Application using Angular 6 to design the process and core java to handle the process requests.
- **Description**: Project based on ecommerce site project